



CHRISTIAN MATOS

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer with strong analytical and problem-solving skills. My background in technology and client services has resulted in increasing product usability for clients. My transition into programming and software engineering allows me to continue this using my past experience in tech to better serve the community. My approachable demeanor, work ethic, adaptability, and ability to work well in high-pressure situations allow me to thrive in the ever-changing landscape of the tech industry.

CONTACT

347-551-7715



cmatos5001@gmail.com



https://christian-matos.netlify.app



https://github.com/Chris-m18



https://www.linkedin.com/in/christianrmatos



https://twitter.com/Chris_5001

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- · Ruby on Rails
- Express
- · GitHub/Git
- De-Bugging/Testing
- PostgresSQL
- · Node.js
- MongoDB
- Command Line
- AWS
- Sass

Education

General Assembly, Software Engineering Immersive

Certificate of Completion

April 2020 – July 2020

Relevant Projects

Once Upon a Book | React, Ruby on Rails, PostgresSQL July 2020

- Database that stores descriptions of popular children's books.
- Leveraged a SQL database with Ruby on Rails to create a fullstack application.
- Authentication and full CRUD functionality.

Good Cuisine | React, MongoDB, Express, Sass June 2020

- · Led an engineering and UXDI team in building a React app with CRUDand search functionality.
- The application allows you to find a recipe through two filtering methods and gives you a step by step navigation tool.
- Fully responsive for desktop, tablet, and mobile screens.

Harry Potter Wiki | React, Javascript, CSS May 2020

- A web application that utilized Axios to pull information from potterAPI and HP-API.
- The application shared information on characters in the Harry Potter universe.
- Developed a random number using an algorithm.

Work Experience

Store Manager

Prime Communications AT&T | Apr 2015 - feb 2020

- Generate repeat business through exceptional customer service.
- Train and develop new associates on POS system and key sales tactics.
- Complete profit and loss performance reports.
- · Respond to customer concerns with friendly and knowledgeable service.

Assistant Store Manager

Prime Communications AT&T | Oct 2014 - Apr 2015

- Complete all daily tasks and special assignments with an efficient and quality-driven approach.
- · Assigned work to team members based on company needs, personal strengths and job knowledge.